W. R. "Bob" Poage Texas Development papers, Inclusive: 1913-1979, undated, Bulk: 1946-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
W. R. "Bob" Poage Texas Development papers
Inclusive: 1913-1979, undated, Bulk: 1946-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
1D
Poage, W. R. (William Robert), 1899 - 1987
31 document boxes and 2 oversized boxes.
This collection contains reports, pamphlets, articles, and other literary productions accumulated by U.S. Representative Bob Poage. The materials relate to the development of Texas, particularly in the areas of agriculture, education, energy, healthcare, immigration, transportation, and water resources.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
William Robert “Bob” Poage, the son of William Allen Poage and Helen Wheeler Conger, was born on December 28, 1899 in Waco, Texas. The Poage family moved to Throckmorton County shortly thereafter where William A. Poage worked as a rancher and cattleman. The Poages eventually returned to Waco in 1913. Five years later, in 1918, Poage graduated from Waco High School and joined the U.S. Navy as an apprentice seaman during the waning months of World War I.
After the war, Poage briefly attended classes at the University of Texas and the University of Colorado at Boulder before enrolling at Baylor University. In 1921, he graduated with a bachelor’s degree in geology. Poage taught geology from 1922 to 1924, while simultaneously working on his law degree. In 1924, he earned his law degree from Baylor University and gained admittance to the Texas Bar.
In that same year, Poage ran for political office, winning a seat in the Texas House of Representatives. He served in the Texas House from 1925 to 1929, all while practicing law in Waco and teaching at Baylor Law School. In 1928, Poage attempted but lost a bid for a seat in the Texas Senate and briefly returned to civilian life. In 1931, Poage sought to fill a Senate seat vacated by Edgar Witt. He won the special election this time, ultimately serving in the Texas Senate from 1931 to 1937.
Striving to increase his political influence, Poage tried to unseat U.S. Representative O. H. Cross of the 11th Congressional District of Texas. Poage lost in 1934 but succeeded in defeating Cross in 1936. It was to be the start of a long-tenured career for the Texas Democrat. On February 14, 1938, amidst his political successes, Poage married Frances Lenoir Cotton.
Poage served in the U.S. House from 1937 until his retirement in 1978, often running unopposed in the biennial elections. Drawing from his childhood experiences and education, Poage championed life in rural America, seeking improvements such as water and telephone services and helping to establish the Rural Electrification Administration. Often referred to as “Mr. Agriculture”, Poage was a key member of the House Agriculture Committee from 1941 to 1978, chairing the committee from 1967 to 1974. Upon his retirement from the House in 1978, Poage was succeeded by Democrat Marvin Leath.
The W. R. Poage Legislative Library was opened in September 1979 in honor of Representative Poage and serves as the repository for his personal and congressional papers. Poage wrote five books during his lifetime including three in retirement: After the Pioneers (1969), Politics-Texas Style (1974), How We Lived (1980), McLennan County Before 1980 (1981), and his autobiography, My First 85 Years (1985).
Poage passed away during open-heart surgery in Temple, Texas, on January 3, 1987, and is buried in Waco’s Oakwood Cemetery.
Scope and Content
The chronology of this collection extends from 1913 to 1979, although the vast majority of materials fall within the years Bob Poage served in the U.S. House of Representatives (1937-1978). These materials represent secondary research and reports accumulated by Poage. Both series pertain to the development of Texas's infrastructure and natural resources.
Series I. General covers a wide range of topics not specifically related to Texas's water resources. Some of the most well-represented subjects include agriculture, education, energy, healthcare, and transportation. The folders in this series are arranged alphabetically by topic.
Series II. Water Resources, the largest series in the collection, relates solely to Texas's waterways including its rivers, tidelands, and basins. Issues such as water conversation, the construction of dams, desalinization, wastewater, and ownership of submerged lands are covered thoroughly in this series. These folders are arranged alphabetically by the individual or organization who created the materials.
Arrangement
The W. R. "Bob" Poage papers have been processed previously, most notably in 1995. Detailed finding aids and folder listings existed prior to this latest round of processing.
Due to the large size of the collection, the W. R. "Bob" Poage papers are being divided into six new collections based on the existing series outline. The materials in the Texas Development papers were originally housed in Boxes #1090-1129. Some loose materials have also been integrated with these files. The collection is now arranged into two series: I. General and II. Water Resources.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 1D. Acquired 1961-08-01
Related Resources
Items in related collections
W. R. "Bob" Poage Personal papers, Inclusive: 1838-2008, undated, Bulk: 1937-1978
William Robert "Bob" Poage Papers
W. R. "Bob" Poage State Legislative papers, Inclusive: 1923-1971, undated, Bulk: 1933-1936
Mattie Mae McKee papers, Inclusive: 1940-2018, undated, Bulk: 1968-1991, 2008-2016
Related references
Duggan, Laura Woolsey. “Poage, William Robert.” Handbook of Texas Online, accessed June 11, 2019.
Pearson, Richard. “Former U.S. Rep. William R. (Bob) Poage Dies.” Washington Post, January 4, 1987.
Poage, W. R. My First 85 Years. Waco, TX: Texian Press, 1985.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Poage, W. R. (William Robert), 1899-1987.
Subjects (Organizations)
Texas Water Development Board.; United States. Army. Corps of Engineers.; United States. Congress. House.; United States. Department of the Interior.
Subjects
Agriculture -- Texas.; Community development -- Texas.; Education--Texas.; Emigration and immigration--Texas.; Energy policy--Texas.; Medical care--Texas.; Natural resources--Texas.; Submerged lands -- Texas.; Transportation--Texas.; Water resources development -- Texas.
Genres
Albums (Books); Articles.; Booklets.; Legal documents.; Pamphlets.; Proposals.; Publications.; Reports.; Surveys (documents)
- General, 1927-1979, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  Series I. General primarily consists of booklets, reports, and other literary productions pertaining to the development of Texas's infrastructure. These documents, in contrast to those found in Series II, do not relate to the state's water resources. Most of the materials are secondary in nature. Representative Poage did not contribute to them directly, rather, he would have used them for research.
  The folders in this series are arranged alphabetically according to subject matter then chronologically within each topic. Agriculture, education, energy, healthcare, and transportation are a few of the more prominent issues addressed. Overall, the series is in good condition.
  - Agriculture, “Cotton Production in Texas”, Texas Agricultural Extension Service, 1959 September (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, 1973 Texas County Statistics (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, Annual Progress Report, Natural Fibers and Food Protein Commission of Texas, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture, Annual Report, Texas Agricultural Experiment Station, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture, Annual Report, Texas Agricultural Experiment Station, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Air Transportation, Southwest Metroplex, Airport and Lifestyle Packet, 1968-1978, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Air Transportation, Publications, Dallas-Fort Worth as Major Trading Center (1 of 2), 1977-1978, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Air Transportation, Publications, Dallas-Fort Worth as Major Trading Center (2 of 2), 1977-1978, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Art, Advertisement, “Bluebonnets and Cactus: An Album of Southwestern Paintings by Porfirio Salinas”, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Austin, Report, “Austin and Its Future: The Challenge of Growth”, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Books, Texana Catalog, 1964 Fall (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Books, Publisher Catalogs (1 of 2), 1970-1972, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Books, Publisher Catalogs (2 of 2), 1970-1972, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Books, From Texas Catalog, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cattle, Magazine, The Texas Longhorn, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Census Data, Report, “Selected Demographic Characteristics from Census Data-Fourth Count”, 1972 August (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Centennial, Booklet, Texas Centennial Exhibition Held at the Library of Congress, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Central Texas, Study, “Central Texas: An Area of Economic Expansion”, 1951 June (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Childhood, Report, “Child Development Policy for Texas”, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Childhood, Report, “Community Indicators: Improving Community Management”, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Childhood, Book, 78 Things You Need to Know About Texas Children, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Constitution, “Constitution of the State of Texas from The Texas Almanac”, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Constitution, Report, “The Constitution of Texas and the Administrative Structure of the State”, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Constitution, Report, “A New Constitution for Texas”, 1973 November (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Constitution, Report, “A New Constitution for Texas: Text, Explanation, Commentary”, 1973 November (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Constitution, Report, “A New Constitution: Separate Statements of Commission Members”, 1973 December (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cooke County, “The Geology of Cooke County, Texas”, University of Texas Bulletin, 1927 March 8 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Coryell County, Report, “Long-Range County Program”, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Cottonseed, Thesis, Cottonseed Intake in Elderly, Kathy Stephens (1 of 2), 1974 August (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Cottonseed, Thesis, Cottonseed Intake in Elderly, Kathy Stephens (2 of 2), 1974 August (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Cottonseed, Petition, Rogers Delinted Cottonseed Company and Texas A&M University (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Cottonseed, Petition, Rogers Delinted Cottonseed Company and Texas A&M University (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Cottonseed, Petition, Rogers Delinted Cottonseed Company and Texas A&M University (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Crime, Annual Report, Texas Organized Crime Prevention Council, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Crime, Reports, “Criminal Justice Plan for Texas” (Volumes 1 and 2), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Crime, Report, “Criminal Justice Plan for Texas”, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Crime, Report, “1979 Criminal Justice Plan” (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Crime, Survey, “Texas Crime Poll”, 1979 Spring (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cultural Basin Commission, Report, “Developing South Texas”, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Cultural Basin Commission, Report, “Strategies for Economic Growth” (Volume 1), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Cultural Basin Commission, Report, “Strategies for Economic Growth” (Volume 2), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Cultural Basin Commission, Report, “Strategies for Economic Growth” (Volume 3), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cultural Basin Commission, Report, “Regional Human Resource Development Project Phase II Report”, 1977 January (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Cultural Basin Commission, Report, “Human Resource Development Phase III Report”, 1978 March (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Party, Program, Texas Democratic State Convention, 1978 September 15-16 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Economy, Report, “Updated Overall Economic Development Program for the North East Texas Economic Development District, Inc., 1976 September (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Education, Report, “Education: Texas’ Resource for Tomorrow”, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Education, Minority Report, “Board Recommendations for the Medical Section of the Master Plan for Higher Education in Texas”, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Education, “Statistical Supplement to the Annual Report of the Coordinating Board, Texas College and University System for Fiscal Year 1976”, 1976 December (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Education, Annual Report, Coordinating Board of Texas College and University System, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Education, “Statistical Supplement to the Annual Report of the Coordinating Board, Texas College and University System for Fiscal Year 1977”, 1977 December (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Education, Report, Paperwork Reduction Task Force, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Education, Report, “Upper-Level Institutions and Off-Campus Educational Units of Texas Public Universities”, 1977 March (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Education, Essay, “Fall Headcount Enrollment Forecasts: Texas Postsecondary Educational Institutions, 1978-1987”, 1978 May (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Education, Handbook, Texas Professional Educators, 1978 September-October (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Education, Report, “Texas Higher Education in Transition”, 1978 October (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Employment, Report, “1976 Annual Manpower Report to the Governor” (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Employment, Annual Report, Texas Employment Commission, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Employment, Annual Report, Texas State Manpower Services Council, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Employment, Report, “Texas Occupational Employment Statistics”, 1978 July (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Energy, Brochure, Oil and Gas Development in Foard County, circa 1940 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Energy, Economic Facts on Oil and Gas, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Energy, Executive Summary, “Texas Energy Outlook: The Next Quarter Century”, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Energy, Texas Energy Advisory Council, Correspondence and Resolutions, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Energy, Texas Energy Policy, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Energy, Report, “Texas Lignite”, Phillips Coal Company, 1977 June (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Energy, “Energy Extension Service Proposal”, 1977 June 30 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Energy, Report, “Texas Energy: A Twenty-Five Year History”, 1977 August (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Energy, Reports, Texas Energy Development Fund (Volumes 1 and 2), 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Energy, Report, “Texas Energy Issues 1978” (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Energy, Study Paper, “Explaining Energy Votes in the Ninety-Fourth Congress”, 1978 June (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Environment, Report, “Environmental Impact Statements: Effects on Program Implementation”, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Factories, Texas Plant Location Fact Book, circa 1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Federal Government, Report, Texas Congressional District Data, 1972 April (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Federal Government, “Analysis of President Ford’s Message on Budget Restraint”, 1975 January 10 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Federal Government, Report, “Impacts of Federal Aid on State and Local Governments in Texas”, 1976 August (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Federal Government, Report, “Federal Human Service Programs and Joint Funding Simplification in Texas”, 1978 July (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Health, “Proposal for a Hill Country Health Plan” (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Health, “Proposal for a Hill Country Health Plan” (2 of 3), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Health, “Proposal for a Hill Country Health Plan” (3 of 3), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Health, Annual Report, Operation MEDIHC (Military Experience Directed Into Health Careers), 1976 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Health, Annual Report, Operation MEDIHC (Military Experience Directed Into Health Careers), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Health, Bibliography, “Publications of the Staff”, University of Texas System Cancer Center M.D. Anderson Hospital and Tumor Institute, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Health, Biennial Report, Texas Department of Health Services, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Health, Report, “Hospital Cost Containment: A Reality in Texas”, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Health, Report to the 65th Texas Legislature, “A Summary of Legislation Affecting Texas Hospitals”, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Highways, Report, “Interstate 27 Extension”, Texas Highway Department (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Highways, Report, “Interstate 27 Extension”, Texas Highway Department (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Highways, Book, Texas Citizens Support Adequate Highway Funds (1 of 2), 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Highways, Book, Texas Citizens Support Adequate Highway Funds (2 of 2), 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - History, Reproduction of Texas Declaration of Independence, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - History, “Guide to Official Texas Historical Markers”, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - History, Report, “Historic Preservation in Texas”, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Immigrant Labor, Report, “Origins and Problems of Texas Migratory Farm Labor”, 1940 September (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Immigrant Labor, Report, American GI Forum of Texas and Texas State Federation of Labor, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Immigrant Labor, Report, “Strangers in Our Fields”, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Immigrant Labor, Report, National Hispanic Leadership Conference, 1977 July 20-22 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Industry, Report, “The Economic Feasibility of an Industrial Complex Based Upon Petrochemical Raw Materials”, 1965 September (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Industry, Report, “Potentials for Development: The Texas Beef Industry”, 1965 October (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Industry, Report, “Analysis of World Markets for Texas Products”, 1966 March (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Industry, Report, “Texas Market Trends and PotentialDL1960-2020”, 1967 July (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Industry, Annual Report, Texas Industrial Commission, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Industry, Annual Report, Texas Industrial Commission, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Industry, “Businessman’s Inventory Dallas/Fort Worth 1978 Edition” (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Insurance, Directory, “List of Companies Under the Supervision of the Board of Insurance Companies, State of Texas”, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Jaycees, Hustle Book, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Libraries, Report, “Texas Public Library Statistics for 1971”, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Mapping Advisory Committee, Reports (1 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Mapping Advisory Committee, Reports (2 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Pecan Growers Association, 56th Annual Conference Proceedings, 1977 July 18-20 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Pollution, “Air Quality Analysis: Dallas/Fort Worth Urban Area”, 1975 October (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Pollution, Biennial Report, Texas Air Control Board, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Pollution, Report, “Houston Area Oxidants Study”, 1977 November (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Population, Publication, “A Decade of Population Change in Texas”, 1963 September (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Postal Service, Directory, “Postmasters and Post Offices of the Tenth Congressional District of Texas”, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Poverty, Annual Report, “The Texas Front in the Nation’s Struggle Against Poverty”, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Recreation, Reports, “Texas Outdoor Recreation Plan” (Volumes 1 and 2), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Recreation, Travel Brochure, “Texas: America’s Fun-tier”, circa 1975 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Recreation, “A Guide to Texas Hunting and Sport Fishing Regulations, 1976-1977” (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Revenue Sharing, Report, “Federal General Revenue Sharing and the Finances of Texas State and Local Government”, 1975 July (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Science, Proposal, Resource Center in Science and Engineering for South Central Texas (1 of 7), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Science, Proposal, Resource Center in Science and Engineering for South Central Texas (2 of 7), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Science, Proposal, Resource Center in Science and Engineering for South Central Texas (3 of 7), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Science, Proposal, Resource Center in Science and Engineering for South Central Texas (4 of 7), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Science, Proposal, Resource Center in Science and Engineering for South Central Texas (5 of 7), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Science, Proposal, Resource Center in Science and Engineering for South Central Texas (6 of 7), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Science, Proposal, Resource Center in Science and Engineering for South Central Texas (7 of 7), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Space, Report, “New Mexico and Texas Plan for Support of the Manned Moon Shot” (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Space, Report, “New Mexico and Texas Plan for Support of the Manned Moon Shot” (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - State Government, Brochure, Texas State Library, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - State Government, Fact Sheet, Texas Capitol, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - State Government, “Governmental Guide: Texas Edition”, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - State Government, Book, Programs for People, Governor Preston Smith, 1973 January (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - State Government, Annual Financial Report, State of Texas, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - State Government, Report, “Block Versus Categorical Grants: Views of Texas State Agencies”, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Texas Association of Business, Conference Materials, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Throckmorton County, Brochure, “Where Cattle Grow and Oil Flows”, circa 1958 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Transportation, “Dallas-Fort Worth Regional Transportation Study”, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Transportation, “Dallas-Fort Worth Regional Transportation Study”, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Transportation, Annual Report, Council for Advanced Transportation Studies, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Transportation, “Regional Transportation Study”, Austin, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Transportation, Report, “1977 Transportation Program for North Central Texas” (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Transportation, Report, “1977 Transportation Program for North Central Texas” (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Transportation, Report, “A Metropolitan Transportation Plan for National Energy Contingencies”, 1977 August (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Transportation, Report, “1978 Transportation Program for North Central Texas” (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Transportation, Report, “1978 Transportation Program for North Central Texas” (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Transportation, Report, “1976-78 Unified Work Program for Transportation Planning in the North Central Texas Region”, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - War Casualties, “State Summary of War Casualties [Texas]”, U.S. Navy, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - War Casualties, Report, “World War II Honor List of Dead and Missing: State of Texas”, 1946 June (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Welfare, Report, “The Place of Social Services in Welfare Policy: An Assessment of Federal Policy Changes and Their Impact on Texas”, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Welfare, Report, “Prevocational Training for Welfare Recipients”, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 3)